[{"answer": "The Abbot will be pleased", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 3, "question": "Don't what", "qsentId": 2}, {"answer": "Don't", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 5, "question": "Please don't tell him.  At least until I know if there's an infection", "qsentId": 4}, {"answer": "Your vehicle crash landed.  Brother my friend found you and brought you here", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 7, "question": "This is the Minorite Abbey within the manmade orbiter Arceon", "qsentId": 6}, {"answer": "You know that's how the devil works. Deception", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 9, "question": "You haven't seen a woman in thirty years. Where does this feeling originate, my friend", "qsentId": 8}, {"answer": "Get to my ship and get off this Satellite", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 11, "question": "We can't what", "qsentId": 10}, {"answer": "The reason we are out here.  Like the Monks who guarded Monastery Libraries on remote islands off that place during the First Plague", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 13, "question": "Some of these books survived the burning of the Libraries of that place.  They contain knowledge that exists in no other record.  Their value is unestimable", "qsentId": 12}, {"answer": "I've fought these creatures twice before.  It take a lot to kill these things.  Heavy artillery", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 15, "question": "How about something we can make weapons from?  Do you have anything like that", "qsentId": 14}, {"answer": "See my bag", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 17, "question": "Just a book", "qsentId": 16}, {"answer": "What's that book", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 19, "question": "I don't buy", "qsentId": 18}, {"answer": "Just a book", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 21, "question": "It's just... a medical book I might need", "qsentId": 20}, {"answer": "Yeah", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 23, "question": "Go ahead and what", "qsentId": 22}, {"answer": "We're supposed to die here.  That's the point", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 25, "question": "The punishment for our crime was death", "qsentId": 24}, {"answer": "Here's the plan", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 27, "question": "Forget the books", "qsentId": 26}, {"answer": "It means I don't know how long I was in hyper sleep", "docId": "Alien-3.txt", "asentId": 29, "question": "It means my clock isn't working.  We have to get out of here.  Even if he was right this ship's onboard computer is filled with man's knowledge", "qsentId": 28}]